pakdiscussion.com 2010-09-26

# Privacy Policy

Pakdiscussion.com provides interactive environments on the Internet to enable members to express themselves and share their ideas and interests by creating and participating in discussion-based forums. One of our goals at Pakdiscussion.com is to respect the privacy rights of anyone who joins Pakdiscussion.com or visits any of our forums. Except as set forth within this privacy statement and within the scope of our community and content guidelines, we do not release personally identifiable information about our individual members and visitors without their permission. Our view is that our members and visitors are the ones who should generally control whether or not they share any personal information and how that information is used if it is shared. Furthermore, we believe that it is our responsibility to provide something of value in exchange for any information shared - in our case, discussion forums, email, and other free services. We appreciate your interest in and support of Pakdiscussion.com and pledge to you our continued commitment to make our services better and better while enabling you - our members and visitors - to be comfortable with respect to your online privacy. To contact Pakdiscussion.com about technical problems, to report a violation of our guidelines, to inquire about advertising within our domain, or any other item of interest or concern, please send us an email admin@pakdiscussion.com. 

Pakdiscussion.com respects the privacy of all those who spend any amount of time in our forums. We do collect information from our members and visitors. This is a statement of the use of the information that we collect, and if or how any of it is disseminated. If you have questions regarding this Statement of Privacy or feel that Pakdiscussion.com has violated it in any way, please contact us at admin@pakdiscussion.com, so that we may address this issue. 

**Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: clicksor, cubics etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies. 

**Membership Validity?**

We reserve the right to delete any message, ban any member for any or no reason whatsoever. Members found to be abusing the contact form, using it for commercial purposes, or otherwise breaking the Community Guidelines will have his/her membership suspended. 

**Children below 13 DO NOT Register**

The Federal Trade Commission's Children Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) require that Web Sites are to obtain parental consent before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from children under 13. If you are below 13 then you cannot use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13. 

**Terms of Service**

This page outlines the core principals which you must abide by when using this website. In the circumstances which this document uses the terms "We", "pakdiscussion", "Us" or "Pakdiscussion.com" outlines the owners, moderators and administrators which have created, developed and moderated this website (www.pakdiscussion.com). 

In the Events that the terms "You" or "Users" arise in this document then you should clearly understand that this means the users browsing the website.

The term "the website" clearly defines "www.pakdiscussion.com".

Most of the videos found on our site are found freely available around the web on sites such as Zshare.net, Youtube Etc. We make no guarantees or promises in our service and take no liability for our users actions. We are not affiliated nor claim to be affiliated with any of the owners of videos/streams played on our site. All content is copyright of their respective owners. 

We urge all copyright owners, to recognize that links contained within this site are located somewhere else on the web. The embedded link points to the location of the video on the web. Please direct all copyright infringement issues to the companies that host these files (Youtube, Zshare, MegaVideo etc) If you still want to contact us email us at admin@pakdiscussion.com. 

This document contains the Terms and Conditions of using this website. 

**1\. Liabilities**

1.1 Although every care is taken in the preparation of the website, you acknowledge that it is not technically possible to run the website free of all faults, and we give no warranties as to the continued operation of the website and accept no liability for any time the website is not operational due to faults or maintenance. 

1.2 You understand that the information supplied to us is by a third party and as such, we cannot take responsibility for this information. We fully appreciate the work of our third parties and take no credit for their efforts. 

1.3 The material on the website is designed to comply with Pakistani law and we cannot be held responsible for any non-compliance with applicable local laws in any other jurisdiction. 

**2\. Links to and from this Website**

2.1 The Website may contain hypertext links to websites operated by third parties. We do not have control of such websites and you therefore acknowledge that we have no responsibility or liability for their content. 

**3\. Use of information**

3.1 The information provided from this website is not owned by us. In this instance we cannot take responsibility for what you do with this information and may be re-distributed with consent of its original authors.
